Inventory of the Grani articles submitted for publication
Hoover Institution Archives
- "Professionaly postkommunizma," Andrei Novikov, circa 1990 (Box 10: 24)
- "Tak nazyvaemaia bor'ba s oligarkhami," Andrei Novikov, circa 1995 (Box 10: 25)
- "Kontrterroristicheskii sindrom," Andrei Novikov, circa 1995 (Box 10: 26)
- "Drozh' zemli," Levon Khechoian, circa 1995 (Box 10: 27)
- "Baron fon Grevenits," Lidiia Golovkova, circa 1995 (Box 10: 28)
- "Navstrechu svetlomu luchu," Irina Kiseleva, circa 1985 (Box 10: 29)
- "Daniil Andreev i russkaia dukhovnaia poeziia,: Boris Romanov, 1997-1998 (Box 10: 30)
- "U vrat Kieva," Georgii Avisov, circa 1995 (Box 10: 31)
- "Aborigeny, " Aleksandr Novyi, circa 2000 (Box 10: 32)
- "Kanva," Anatolii Prelovskii, circa 1995 (Box 10: 33)
- ""Rossiia i Chechnia: istoriia konfrontatsii," John Dunlop, 2001 (Box 10: 334)
- "My uzhe ne raby," Nikita Moravskii, circa 1991 (Box 10: 35)
- "Obshchina," Igor' Mannikov, 1998 (Box 10: 36)
- "Diagnosis dubitus," Ian Torchinskii, circa 1995 (Box 10: 37)
- "Polia Megido," Dmitrii Shliapontokh, circa 1995 (Box 10: 37)
- "Moi neokonchennyi romans," Grigorii Iaremenko, circa 1995 (Box 10: 39)
- "Stolknovenie chechentsev s Rossiei ," John Dunlop, circa 2000 (Box 10: 40)
- "Nad propast'iu v Moslve i mire," Vladimir Lazarev, 1998 (Box 10: 41)
- "Strana fantazii-vechnosti strana," Igor' Mannikov, circa 1995 (Box 10: 42)
- "K 80-letiiu Leona Toma," Anna Tom, 2001 (Box 10: 43)
- "Narod ponial nas i prostil," Aleksei Karamzin, circa 1995 (Box 10: 44)
- "Organicheskii tragizm golosa," Konstantin Iusupov, 2001 (Box 10: 45)
- "Doroga N.6666," Vladimir Nikolaev, circa 2000 (Box 10: 46)
- "Geroi na svoem meste," Natal'ia Bragina, circa 1995 (Box 10: 47)
- "Oktiabr'skii sad," Dmitrii Vetvin, 2000 (Box 10: 48)
- "Ocherko o Iurii Zavadskom i Faine Ranevskoi ," Valentin Shkol'nikov, 1997 (Binder 10: 49)
- "Vspomiani, starik-istorik, vspomiani o nas," Alla Ktorova, 2000 (Box 10: 50)
- "Pamiati Nadezhdy Ivanovny Kataevoi -Lytkinoi ", 2001 (Box 11: 1)
- ""O druzhbe s A. I. Tsvetaevoi ,"Grigorii Korin, 1992 (Box 11: 2)
- "Leningradskaia snegurochka," Irina Kisileva, 1999 (Box 11: 3)
- "Tri samuraia v osazhdennoi kreposti," Dmitrii Pasternak, 1999 (Box 11: 4)
- "Pro sebia o Brodskom," Aleksandr Levintov, circa 2000 (Box 11: 5)
- "Boris Nikolaevich Shartino, ' Rostislav Polchaninov, 2002 (Box 11: 6)
- "Syn Epikura na moskovskoi kukhne," Iurii Druzhnikov, 2002 (Box 11: 7)
- "Liudskie poteri Rossii i SSSR v voi nakh i vooruzhennykh konfloktakh XX veka," Boris Sokolov, circa1995 (Box 11: 8)
- "O vstrechakh s A. Pekurovskoi ," Zhilkina Tat'iana, 1998 (Box 11: 9)
- "Dovlatov (plius-minus) mif," Asia Pekurovskaia, 1996 (Box 11: 10)
- "Mysli o budushchem strany," Boris Pushkarev i Lev Nusberg, 1986 (Box 11: 11)
- "Atomniki," Aleksandr Dolgopolov, circa 1995 (Box 11: 12)
- "Slovo ob Antonenko-Davidoviche, Aleksandr Khakhulin, circa 1990 (Box 11: 13)
- "Prazdnik," Gennadii Val'dberg, 1984 (Box 11: 14)
- "Metapsokhoz ili zhenit'ba Kautskogo," Andrei Borodin, 1988 (Box 11: 15)
- "Budni "tridtsat' sed'mogo goda," Naum Korzhavin, circa 1995 (Box 11: 16)
- "Stepnaia doroga," Aleksandr Gubarev, 1961 (Box 11: 17)
- "Moia Estoniia," Mark Popovskii, 1987 (Box 11: 18)
- "Otkuda kazaki na levom beregu Dnestra," Anatolii Kiselev, 1992 (Box 11: 19)
- "S imenem Boga vosstan' Rossiia", circa 1980 (Box 11: 20)
- " V stremnine Dona, Viktor Rastopchin, circa 1980 (Box 11: 21)
- "Kak ia borolsia za perestroiku i chto iz etogo vyshlo," Aleksandr Sarychev, 1986-1990 (Box 11: 23)
- "Moei strane," Nonna Belavina, circa 1990 (Box 11: 23)
- "Otkrytyi otvet na stikhotvorenie R. Rozhdestvennskogo,Spetsialisty iz Rosii," napechataannoe v "Komsomol'skoi pravde" v fevrale 1964 goda," Aleksandr Bek, circa 1964 (Boxes 11: 24)
- "P. Vostokovu," A.F., 1960 (Box 11 :25)
- "Mart," Iurii Maev, 1944 (Box 11: 26)
- "O nauke sovetskoi i amerikanskoi ," Aleksandr Rashin, 1984 (Box 11: 27)
- "Drugoe mnenie," L. Rebrov, 1984 (Box 11: 28)
- "Fragmenty semeinoi khroniki," Rudol'f Ryzhikov, 1997 (Box 11: 29)
- "Iz zapisnoi knizhki," Vladimir Lazarev, 2000-2001 (Box 11: 30)
- "Iz knigi chetverostishii," Ritalii Zaslavskii, circa 1980
- "Pis'mo Borisu Sergeevichu Pushkarevu," Sergei Utekhin, 2000 (Box 11: 32)
- "Chlenam soveta," S. Utekhin, 1997 (Box 11: 33)
- "Famil'nyi obychai," Ekaterina Filatova, circa 2000 (Box 11: 34)
- "Ne ostanovit'sia li?" iz perepiski N. V. Ustrialova i kniagini L. V. Golitsynoi," O. A. Vorob'ev, 1999 (Box 11: 34, Binder 11: 35)
- "Iz vospominanii o Sibirskom Osvage," O. A. Vorob'ev, 2000 (Box 11: 36)
- "Revoliutsionnyi front," N. Ustrialov, 1917 (Box 12: 1)
- "Na ch'ei storone istoricheskaia pravda"" Boris Gershunskii, circa 1995 (Box 12: 2)
- "My vse zhivem v predchuvstvii tepla," book cove, rElena Zhilkina, circa 1995 (Box 12: 2)
- Untitled, circa 1990 (Box 12: 4)
- Untitled, circa 1995 (Box 12: 5)
- Pamiati N. B. Tomashevskogo , circa 1995 (Box 12: 6)
- Pusti, mekhanik kino naoborot!, circa 1990 (Box 12: 7, Box 12: 6)
- Untitled, Vladimir Skrebitskii, 1990 (Box 12: 7)
- Untitled, Vladimir Korin, circa 1985 (Box 12: 8)
- Proshloe I problemy russkogo protestanizma, Tatiana Nikolskaya, circa 1990 (Box 12: 9)
- Sakharov, circa 1990 (Box 12: 10)
- Pisma I. A. Buninu, Boris Zaitsev, 1922 (Box 12: 11)
- Pisma Marianny Shabat k Natale Belinkovoi-Iablokovoi, 1990-1995 (Box 12: 12)
- Den rozhdeniia Kharbina, L. I. Chuguevskii, 1999 (Box 12: 13)
- Zerno, vokrug kotorogo.., Vladimir Tsukanikhin, 1999 (Box 12: 14)
- Molodoi frantsiskanets, Nikolai Gumilev, undated (Box 12: 15)
- Eshche raz o russkoi idée, Sergei Utekhin, circa 1995 (Box 12: 16)
- Letter to the editor, Osip Borisovich Spasov, 1978 (Box 12: 17)
- Organicheskii tragizm golosa I slova, Konstantin Isupov, 2001 (Box 12: 18)
- Zakon kriticheskoi massy, Vladimir Tsukanikhin, 1999 (Box 12: 19)
- Vsevolod Vladimirovich Selivanovskii (1925-1988), R. Polchaninov, 1999 (Box 12: 20)
- Zelenyi ostrovok, Aleksei Ivin, circa 1980 (Box 12: 22)
- Tserkovnyi raskol v Sankhae, Dionosii Pozdniaev, circa 1995 (Box 12: 23)
- Solntse skvoz oblaka, Nadezhda Boltianskaia, circa 1995 (Box 12: 24)
- "Otechestvo," Aleksandr Sobolev, circa 2000 (Box 12: 25)
- "Salo v shokolade," Iakov Ivanov and Garri Tokun, 1997 (Box 12 :26)
- "In Memory of Alexander Pushkin's Bicentennial Birthday," Alex Karamzin, 1999 (Box 12: 27)
- Stikhi, Nataliia Anufrieva, 1949-1954 (Box 12: 28)
- "Daniil Andreev i russkaia dukhovnaia poeziia," Boris Romanov, 1997-1998 (Box 12: 29)
- "Iraida Legkaia i ee stikhi," Vladimir Agenosov and Mikhail Pavlovets, 1999 (Box 12: 30)
- "Dvor," Klavdiia Leibova, circa 2000 (Box 12: 31)
- "Chernyi kot," detektiv gazeta, 2000 (Box 12: 32)
- "Vozvrashchenie Anatoliia Kuznetsova," Igor' Minutko, circa 2000 (Box 12: 33)
- "Moi nabliudeniia i mysli o narode i religii v SSSR," L. Sabaneev, circa 1995 (Box 12: 34)
- "Sovetskii grazhdanin," Soliannikov (Ushakov), circa 1970 (Box 13: 1)
- "Tikhon Shumilkin," Vladimir Lazarev, Ol'ga Tuganova, 2004 (Box 13: 2)
- "O Staline mudrom," Naum Korzhavin, circa 1980 (Box 13: 3)
- "Istoriia moei zhizni," Aleksei E. Pilatskii, 1965 (Box 13: 4)
- "Etot strashnyi, strashnyi russkii natsionalizm, " O. Poliakov, circa 1985 (Box 13: 5)
- "Povest' vozrodivsheisia nadezhdy," Oleg G. Poliakov, 1986 (Box 13: 6)
- Translated poetry, undated (Box 13: 7)
- "Ideia obshchei sud'by," Mikhail Nazarov, 1992 (Box 13: 8)
- "Russkaia sud'ba,"Valentina Senkevich, 1989 (Box 13: 9)
- "Evtushenko v San Frantsisko," Mikhail Lemkhin, circa 1985 (Box 13: 10)
- Mikhail Ponomarev's (Volin) letters, 1989-1991 (Box 13: 11)
- Samizdat izdatel'stva "Posev", 1989 (Box 13 :12)
- Archiv zhurnala "Grani", 2002 (Box 13: 13)